coincommunity.com 2010-05-22

# Coin Forum, Numismatic Education, and Collecting Information | Coin Community

Home > Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

This privacy policy deals with personally-identifiable information (referred to as "data" below) that may be collected by Coin Community. This policy does not apply to other entities that are not owned or controlled by Coin Community, nor does it apply to persons that are not employees or agents of Coin Community, or that are not under Coin Community's control.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, we make use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
We use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include [Google Adsense](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html), [eBay](http://pages.ebay.com/help/policies/privacy-policy.html), [Commission Junction](http://www.cj.com/privacy_web_user.html), and [Amazon](http://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html?ie=UTF8&nodeId=468496) among others. The parties providing the advertising do not have access to this site's cookies. These parties usually use non-personally-identifiable or anonymous codes to obtain information about your visits to this site. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on Coin Community send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Coin Community's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

**Editing or deleting your account information**  
You are provided with the ability to edit the information stored for your user account information during registration, by visiting your user account profile. You can request that your user account be deleted; to do so, please contact the site administrator. Content or other data that you may have provided, and that is not stored within your user account, such as articles published, may continue to remain on the site at Coin Community's discretion, even after your user account is deleted. 

**No gaurantees**  
While this privacy policy states standards for maintenance of data, and while efforts will be made to meet the said standards, Coin Community is not in a position to guarantee compliance with these standards. There may be factors beyond the site editor's control that may result in disclosure of data. Consquently, Coin Community offers no warranties or representations as regards maintenance or non-disclosure of data.

## Popular Collector Coins

Disclaimer: While a tremendous amount of effort goes into ensuring the accuracy of the information contained in this site, Coin Community assumes no liability for errors. Copyright 2005 - 2010 Coin Community Family- all rights reserved worldwide. Use of any images or content on this website without prior written permission of Coin Community or the original lender is strictly prohibited.   
Contact Us | Privacy Policy
